{
	"response_code": "0",
	"results": [
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In the anime Initial D, how does Takumi Fujiwara describe a drift?",
			"correct_answer": "&#039;. . . the front tires slide so the car won&#039;t face the inside&#039;",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"&#039;. . . the wheels lose traction, making the car slide sideways&#039;"
				,
				"&#039;. . . the car oversteers through a curve, causing it to turn faster&#039;"
				,
				"&#039;. . . you turn a lot&#039;"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In the anime, &quot;Full Metal Panel&quot;, who is Kaname&#039;s best friend?",
			"correct_answer": "Kyoko Tokiwa",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Melissa Mao"
				,
				"Ren Mikihara"
				,
				"Teletha &quot;Tessa&quot; Testarossa"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In &quot;Highschool of the Dead&quot;, where did Komuro and Saeko establish to meet after the bus explosion?",
			"correct_answer": "Eastern Police Station",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"The Center Mall"
				,
				"Komuro&#039;s House"
				,
				"On The Main Bridge"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Which of the following countries does &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders&quot; not take place in?",
			"correct_answer": "Philippines",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"India"
				,
				"Pakistan"
				,
				"Egypt"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "What year was &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure: Phantom Blood&quot; first released?",
			"correct_answer": "1987",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"2013"
				,
				"1983"
				,
				"1995"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "What is the last line muttered in the anime film &quot;The End of Evangelion&quot;?",
			"correct_answer": "&quot;How disgusting.&quot;",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"&quot;Idiot, I won&#039;t let you kill me!&quot;"
				,
				"&quot;Nothing.&quot;"
				,
				"&quot;Goddammit, Shinji.&quot;"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Winch of these names are not a character of JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure?",
			"correct_answer": "JoJo Kikasu",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Jean-Pierre Polnareff"
				,
				"George Joestar"
				,
				"Risotto Nero"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Which of these anime have over 7,500 episodes?",
			"correct_answer": "Sazae-san",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Naruto"
				,
				"One Piece"
				,
				"Chibi Maruko-chan"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Which song was the callsign for Stefan Verdemann&#039;s KWFM radio station in Urasawa Naoki&#039;s &quot;Monster&quot;?",
			"correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"What a Wonderful World"
				,
				"When You Wish Upon A Star"
				,
				"Singing In The Rain"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Medaka Kurokami from &quot;Medaka Box&quot; has what abnormality?",
			"correct_answer": "The End",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Perfection"
				,
				"Sandbox"
				,
				"Fairness"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Akatsuki&#039;s subclass in &quot;Log Horizon&quot; is what?",
			"correct_answer": " Tracker",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Assassin"
				,
				"Scribe"
				,
				"Apprentice"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In &quot;One Piece&quot;, who is the girl who overcame her enslaved past and became an agent of an army to fight the corrupt government?",
			"correct_answer": "Koala",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Boa Hancock"
				,
				"Nico Robin"
				,
				"Emporio Ivankov "
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In &quot;One Piece&quot;, what does &quot;the Pirate King&quot; mean to the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
			"correct_answer": "Freedom",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Promise"
				,
				"Adventure"
				,
				"Friendship"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In &quot;One Piece&quot;, who confirms the existence of the legendary treasure, One Piece?",
			"correct_answer": "Edward &quot;Whitebeard&quot; Newgate",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Former Marine Fleet Admiral Sengoku"
				,
				"Pirate King Gol D Roger"
				,
				"Silvers Rayleigh"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In what year did the manga &quot;Ping Pong&quot; begin serialization?",
			"correct_answer": "1996",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"2014"
				,
				"2010"
				,
				"2003"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Which one of these characters is from &quot;Legendz : Tale of the Dragon Kings&quot;?",
			"correct_answer": "Shiron",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Jack"
				,
				"Axia"
				,
				"Drum"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In the &quot;Dragon Ball&quot; franchise, what is the name of Goku&#039;s brother?",
			"correct_answer": "Raditz",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Gohan"
				,
				"Vegeta"
				,
				"Bardock"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Which person from &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure&quot; does NOT house a reference to a band, artist, or song earlier than 1980?",
			"correct_answer": "Giorno Giovanna",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Josuke Higashikata"
				,
				"Jolyne Cujoh"
				,
				"Johnny Joestar"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In &quot;Hunter x Hunter&quot;, which of the following is NOT a type of Nen aura?",
			"correct_answer": "Restoration",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Emission"
				,
				"Transmutation"
				,
				"Specialization"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "In &quot;Hunter x Hunter&quot;, what are members in Killua&#039;s family known for being?",
			"correct_answer": "Assassins",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Bandits"
				,
				"Hunters"
				,
				"Ninjas"
				
			]
		}
	]
}